Hamza Chokri

Industrial Engineer/Full Stack JS Developer/Master Degree In Intelligent Decision Making Strategies





Profile

A highly effective and goal-oriented industrial engineer with two years of experience in the industry, Strong organizational and leadership competencies with a proven record of accomplishment in delivering excellent outcomes. My goal is joining companies to work on accelerating industry 4.0 transformation.

Professional Experience

Quality Audit Engineer, SARTEX GROUP

03/2019 - 08/2021

Km1 Route de Sousse, Ksar Hellal 5016,

Tunisia

- Evaluate the internal quality of the products.
- management of indicators and the quality dashboard of internal products and subcontractors.
- Do weekly analyzes of Non-Qualities and measurement risks.
- Identify customer needs and requirements, and define procedures, instructions, and work methods related to the control of products.
- participate in continuous improvement projects.
- Completed project:integration of a measurement decision support module.
- participate in continuous improvement projects.

Full Stack Js Developer Training (MERN Stack)., GoMyCode

09/2020 - 01/2021

1 Place Tahar Haddad, 1 Tunis 1053, Tunis

1053, Tunisia

Development of a web application for the sale of food products, using :React js, Express, Mongoose, MongoDB,JWT,OAuth 2.0,Push notifications, BootStrap, Adminbro.

industrial internship, Prysmian Group

02/2018 - 08/2018

Mongi Slim, Menzel Bou Zelfa, Nabeul,

Tunisia

Study and improvement of the productivity of a fiber optic production line. key word:Lean Manufacturing ,

Industrial internship, Prysmian Group

06/2017 - 07/2017

Mongi Slim, Menzel Bou Zelfa, Nabeul,

Tunisia

Measurement of performance indicators of a production line and implementation of a maintenance dashboard.

Education

Master Degree In Intelligent Decision Making Strategies.,

2021 - present | Tunis, Tunisia

Higher Institute of Management of Tunis

Industrial Engineer Diploma,

The Higher National Engineering School of Tunis

Physics Chemistry Preparatory diploma,

the Preparatory Institute for Engineering Studies of Gabès, Tunisia

Mathematics High school diploma,

Ibn khaldoun Sidi Aich High school

2015 | Gabes, Tunisia

2018 | Tunis, Tunisia

2013 | Gafsa, Tunisia

Skills

- * Project management skills; Microsoft project
- * Problem solving method; Brainstorming, Pareto, Ishikawa, 5 why, 8D, PDCA, ...
- * Office utilities (Excel, Power point, Word)

SGBDR

MySQL, MariaDB

Style sheet languages

CSS.Less, Sass

Version control software

Git, Github

Markup language

:HTML,XML

Backend framework

Node, JS, Express

API REST

- * Continuous improvement techniques; Kaizen / Six sigma / PDCA /lean manufacturing tools
- * Mechanical design, design and simulation software (Catia, Ms Project, Arena, TIA Portal, Matlab)
- * Communication skills, Team work,
 Organization and moderation of meetings,
 time management

linux container systems

Docker

Front End Library

React , Redux.

Programming languages

JS,TS,PHP, Python, Java, C++,Ceplex.

Dig Data

Hadoop, MapReduce, Spark

SGBD NOSQL

MongoDB, CouchDB, Cassandra

Certificates

- Full Stack |s Developer (MERN Stack)
- Motivation and teams animation.
- SWOT analysis

- PHP OOP/Typescript/React native
- ISO internal quality audit 9001

Languages

English French
Voltaire

Arabic

Interests

^{*}Sport (Footing, Football), *Reading, Traveling (camping, hiking)